# CARL E. YAZBEK

FINANCE & BUSINESS MANAGER

## SOCIAL

linkd.in/carlyazbek

## SKILLS

CONTRACTING FINANCE OPERATIONS PROGRAM MANAGEMENT MARKETING STRATEGY **BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT** RELATIONSHIP BUILDING COMMUNICATION CUSTOMER SERVICE MICROSOFT OFFICE SUITE

# EDUCATION

CSU - FULLERTON

2011 - 2013 **BA: Marketing** 

#### IRVINE VALLEY COLLEGE

2009 - 2011 AA: Business, Computer Information and Applied

**Technologies** 

NORTH WOOD HIGH

2005 - 2009

High School Diploma

# CONTACT

Email: the.egotiator@gmail.com Phone: + (949) 838-5832

#### SUMMARY

Experienced Finance and Business Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the retail and financial industry. Skilled in Credit Review, Contract Execution, Program Management, and Finance Operations. Strong finance professional with a Business BA focused in Marketing from Cal State Fullerton.

#### EXPERIENCE

# TUTTLE CLICK MAZDA | FROM JUNE 2012 - PRESENT Financial & Business Manager

- · Negotiates and executes contracts with clients, financial institutions, and vendors
- Ensures increased sales, cost-savings, profit, superior delivery, and satisfaction.
- · Operates and manages in a fast paced, constantly evolving team environment
- Builds, maintains, and influences business and banking relationships to drive company agenda
- · Provides thought leadership in creating and assessing procedures and initiatives for growth and efficiencies
- · Review Credit Applications, secure loans, and approve delivery of high and low level assets
- Results oriented environment involving strategic planning, problem solving, and sound business judgment

#### MCS SOLUTIONS | FROM MAR 2009 - NOV 2011

IT & Customer Service

- · Developed internal solutions to gain efficiencies, increase productivity, and
- Ensured accessibility for all business applications and end-user programs
- · Responsible for developing client solutions to satisfy clients and achieve growth

#### AWARDS

# BOY SCOUTS OF AMERICA | FROM AUG 2005 - FEB 2009 Eagle Scout

· Raised thousands of dollars, served in many leadership positions, and mentored and led other scouts.

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST